leicestertigers.com 2003-06-26

# Leicester Tigers Official Site

  Privacy Statement and Policy

Your privacy when visiting our website is important to us. We have therefore developed our privacy policy to explain the type of information we collect, what we do with it, and how you can correct or change the information.

Tigers collects two types of information from visitors to our website; 'personal data' and 'aggregated data'.

Personal data is collected when you visit our website and provide us with information about yourself when either applying for Tigers membership or booking into a Tigers event online. This includes giving us your name, address, and other billing information. We also collect your credit card information to enable us to process online a membership application or an event booking, and which we will then charge to your account.

Tigers may place your e-mail address together with any other information you provide on an e-mail contact list. Occasionally, we may send you by e-mail or otherwise, information about the Club, and other activities. You may remove your information from this contacts list at any time simply by sending an e-mail to [tigerzine@tigers.co.uk](mailto:tigerzine@tigers.co.uk?subject=Remove%20my%20Information)

Aggregated data is collected to provide information on traffic patterns on the Tigers website, including how many visitors log into www.tigers.co.uk daily, system administration and to measure the success of specific areas within our website. Tigers collect aggregated data through various methods, including storing IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from www.tigers.co.uk, our servers log your IP address. Tigers never links a visitor's personal details to the IP address attached to the computer the visitor is using. Therefore, although Tigers will log your session using your IP address, you will always remain anonymous to us.

   Security

Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure transactions. Our SSL encrypts all of your personal information including credit card details. All personal information is stored in our secure databases, and access is strictly controlled and limited to certain individuals within Tigers.

  Use of Cookies

Tigers also uses 'persistent cookies' to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that most websites write to a visitor's hard drive for the purposes of record keeping, but also to make improvements and provide updates to visitors based upon which areas of the website are popular, or not. A persistent cookie will remain on a visitor's hard drive until it is deleted. Cookies allow Tigers to measure activity on the site and to help improve your experience as a user. For example, we use cookies to remember your passwords and viewing preferences, thus allowing you to visit various member-only parts of the website without re-registering.
